29/09/2002

IT Support/Networking

Professional summary

Accumulating months of experience in the IT sector, specializing in security. Oversight of IT/OT, network systems, vulnerability scanning, and conducting tests and exploitations. Implementation of mitigation strategies, including patch updates and configuration of Firewalls and VPNs.

Experience

Data Science intern | Wisdom Robotics | 05/2023-08/2023

- Make Report, provide AI, Data mining solutions
- · Crawl, process data from commercials and industry, building dashboard
- Build Al model such as Spam Detection, Recommendation System

Cyber Security Fellowship | OPSWAT | 09/2023-11/2023

- Monitor, identify vulnerabilities among IOT/OT systems, IT server and application
- Work as Penetration tester conduct exploitation over the system
- Assess vulnerabilities, provide mitigations and create ad-hoc report

Skills

Python C++ JavaScript SQL

English communication - TOEIC 835

Database PostgreSQL SQLite

Excel PowerBI Tableau Tools

Software Development

Networking

Education

Embedded system and IOT | HCM UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY & EDUCATION | 08/2020 - 2024 |